<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bound1ess blog</title>
    <description>Welcome to my blog where I talk about programming and IT related stuff.</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 22:52:03 +0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 22:52:03 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To My Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
        <link>/2014/12/04/welcome-to-my-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2014/12/04/welcome-to-my-blog.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Installing Windows 7 on Lenovo G505</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;First of all, you need a proper ISO image. You can get one &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.techverse.net/download-windows-7-iso-x86-x64-microsofts-official-servers/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you should create a &lt;em&gt;bootable USB/DVD disc&lt;/em&gt;. And if you do not know how to do that, 
there are hundreds of good examples available on the Internet, so just do a quick search.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you need to plug in the &lt;em&gt;USB device/DVD disc&lt;/em&gt; that you created and shut down your computer afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now look at your shiny &lt;em&gt;G505&lt;/em&gt;. There is a small button next to the power button (on its right). Press it and wait a little bit.
You should see the startup menu. Choose &lt;em&gt;“BIOS setup”&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now follow these steps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Find &lt;em&gt;“SecureBoot”&lt;/em&gt; option and disable it. Otherwise you will not be able to perform installation.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Now change the boot mode to &lt;em&gt;“Legacy support”&lt;/em&gt; (it is set to &lt;em&gt;“UEFI”&lt;/em&gt; by default). You can not install Windows 7 on UEFI-based computer without the legacy support mode enabled.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You can also change the boot priority to &lt;em&gt;“Legacy first”&lt;/em&gt;, although it is optional (if you want to, you can, but it is not required).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Then change the boot order using &lt;em&gt;Fn+F5, Fn+F6&lt;/em&gt; combinations. You should place your &lt;em&gt;USB device/DVD disc&lt;/em&gt; on top of the list.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now restart your computer and (if you did everything correctly) you will see the Windows 7 installation window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have fun!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
        <link>/2014/12/04/installing-windows-7-on-lenovo-g505.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2014/12/04/installing-windows-7-on-lenovo-g505.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
